Okay, so welcome to this video, let's use PSXX, the impacted library, which we have
already seen in this, so we can use the library and we can move later, laterally from
this machine to another machine, okay. So nothing changes, let's use this command, impacted
PSXX and we need to give the domain here, so this information should be get from the
credential access section and you need to give the username and you need to be the password
for the user, so this, all the information will be gathering from that session and you
need to give the IP address, okay. So basically, you will be giving, you will be giving
the IP address of the target here, so this IP address, you will get from discovery section,
so how you gathered information from multiple tools like advanced IP scanner, and
gave angry IP scanner. So you can develop a small script with inteckett, PSXX, window,
username, password, a small bad file with following IP, which you have seen, okay. So it
will automatically execute, it will give a command prompt to you, to perform, to control
the machine, okay. So now I use the domain and the username as a user and password
as a password, so this is the credentials, which we have and the username, sorry, the IP
address of the machine, so once I give this, it's showing, it created a, uploading a file,
it's, it's uploaded some files like DB, BHY, CAO.exe and that executable was written
in the adventure, so nothing but it will creating a, creating a service and it will be
starting a service, so now we got enough, a privilege, I feel, to run the machine, so if
you can see the privilege of a system-mandated level, because it created a service, elevating
the service account, service control manager. So let's move on to the Windows machine,
so see the Windows machine acting like nothing will happen in this, but if you go to the
event we were and look into the, look into the event logs, let me refresh this, so here
you can see there is a, on, of a service get created, the service name was BH, BHYCAO.exe
and the event ID was 0.045, okay. So if there is any kind of impact execution, if you
notice, there will be a lateral movement that was possible, impact was going on, so there
must be a service that was created, okay. So service will be created and you need to monitor
the 7, 0, 4, 5 events for that, you need to investigate the 7, 0, 4, 5 events, okay.
So while investigating the 7, 0, 4, 5, even you can understand the one service get created
and that was executed in the machine and giving a reverse connection to the attacker.
So this is how you need to troubleshoot the impact librarian in its understand which user
performed the impact execution. So here you can find the username as user, so you can disable
this user and reset the credentials and you can delete this service from the machine, okay.
So let's hop off and we'll move on to the next video.
See you guys, bye bye.